(Sheldon:)Uh, for regular readers
of The New England Journal
of High Energy Physics,
(Sheldon:)I need no introduction.
(Sheldon:)If you're not familiar
(Sheldon:)with that publication,
(Sheldon:)there's a free copy
in your goody bag.
(Sheldon:)Stuart?
Um... (clears throat) Hi.
(Stuart:)I'm Stuart.
(Stuart:)I run a comic bookstore,
(Stuart:)which for financial reasons,
I'm currently living in.
(Stuart:)And I guess
(Stuart:)what I'm hoping for most out
of tonight is a hot shower.
It's very
nice, Stuart.
(Sheldon:)Zack?
(Zack:)I'm Zack, and I'm, uh...
(Howard:)Uh...
(Zack:)Could you come back to me?
(Leonard:)Of course.
(Sheldon:)Barry?
(Barry:)I'm Barry Kwipke, and I'm here
(Barry:)because you told me
there was going to be a whaffle.
(Barry:)When is the whaffle?
(Sheldon:)Patience, patience, Barry.
The whaffle... (clears throat)
The raffle is the grand finale
(Sheldon:)to an evening-long festival
of fun and folly.